streamtuner.li 2017-08-30

# Privacy Policy - Stream TV Online With Stream Tuner

Privacy Policy

We at Stream Tuner are aware of how much you care for the personal information you use and share. , and we appreciate your trust that we will handle it with care and sensibility. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us and will never provide or sell personal information to entities that are outside of the Stream Tuner community.  
By visiting Stream Tuner , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Information Collected  
We gather personal information, such as names, email addresses, and so on., when willfully presented by our guests. The data you give is utilized to satisfy your particular request, unless you provide for us consent to utilize it as a part of an alternate way, for instance, to add you to one of our mailing records.  
Cookies and Web Beacon  
Our site may utilize cookies and/or any web beacon which are valuable for gathering data, for example, program sort and working framework, following the quantity of guests to the site, and seeing how guests utilize the Site.  
Individual data can’t be gathered through cookies and other web beacon, however, if you provided the personal information beforehand, cookies may be fixed to such data. Third parties, for example, our promoters might likewise cookies treats to gather data as a part of the course of serving advertisements to you. Most web programs consequently acknowledge cookies, however you can normally alter your browser settings to decline cookies based on your preference.

Distribution of Information  
We will never share any of your personal information to any third party for promoting purposes. However, we may impart data to legislative organizations and agencies or different organizations supporting us in extortion aversion or examination. We may do so when either allowed or needed by law; attempting to ensure against or counteract real or potential extortion or unapproved exchanges; or, exploring misrepresentation which has effectively occurred.

Our Commitment to Data Security

Your personal data and information’s will be kept secured. Only approved staff of this site (who have consented to keep data secure and classified) have admittance to this data. All messages and pamphlets from this site permit you to withdraw of further mailings.

How to Contact Us  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Stream Tuner Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at admin@StreamTuner.li.

Updates & Effective Date  
We may update this privacy notice from time to time. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our site.  
A notice will be placed on our site to notify you for any changes we made to the Stream Tuner Privacy Policy  
We urge you to occasionally inquire and survey this arrangement so you generally will realize what data we gather, how we utilize it, and to whom we reveal it.
